# **Thomas Giagtzoglou**

tomgia.com 2022587611 tom.giagtzoglou@gmail.com

A technically-minded artist set on exploring the intersection between art and technology. With experience in Game Design and Web Development, and a background as a Bicycle Mechanic, I have a well-rounded set of practical and technological skills. I am passionate about problem-solving, learning, and creating memorable and enjoyable digital experiences. I bring strong skills in communication and deliberate action that can assist any team in working efficiently and getting tasks done correctly, the first time around.

### **Education**

Drexel University Philadelphia, PA Bachelor of Science in Game Design and Production Anticipated Graduation June 2023

Flatiron School Washington, DC Full Stack Web Development September 2018 - January 2019 In person program

Skidmore College Saratoga Springs, NY Pursued a double major in Computer Science and Studio Art September 2017 - May 2018

#### Technical Skills

Software: Adobe Creative Suite, Autodesk Maya, AWS, Git, Google Suite, Substance Suite, Unity. Programming Languages: JavaScript, C#, SQL, GraphQL, Java, Ruby on Rails, HTML, CSS.

## **Employment History**

Brand Knew Los Angeles, CA (Remote) Fullstack Web Developer

Led development for a full stack web application created for a client.

- + Created two 1-1 syncing relationships with 3rd party APIs.
- + Utilized React and Node to develop features of the application following the client's specifications.
- + Responsible for full production deployment, ongoing support, and updates.

Conte's Bike Shop Washington, DC May 2018 - August 2018 Bike Mechanic

- + Repaired, built and specced parts for road, mountain, triathlon, and E-bikes.
- + Focused on working with customers, providing specific services and complex repairs.

City Bikes Washington, DC April 2014 - June 2017

Bike Mechanic and Sales Associate

+ Repaired, built and specced parts for road, mountain, triathlon, and children's bikes.

+ Sold bikes and accessories helped customers choose bikes to fit needs, ran cash register.

#### **Honors and Awards**

- + A. J. Drexel Scholarship
- + AP Scholar With Distinction
- + Outstanding Senior Artist Award

- + Westphal Portfolio Scholarship
- + National Honor Society Member
- + PLTW Engineering Capstone Scholar

June 2019 - Present